Louise Z. Young Photographs MS156
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Negatives and Prints, 1947 -- 1970; MS156.001; 1.0 Linear Feet; 498 Digital Object(s)
  - Commencement - Tufts, 1957; MS156.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
    - Harry Burden, Nils Wessel, and Clarence "Pop" Houston at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00018; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; negatives (photographic); Wessell, Nils Yngve --Houston, Clarence "Pop"
    - Group of honorees and administrators on stage, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00019; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; negatives (photographic); Wessell, Nils Yngve --Houston, Clarence "Pop" --Burden, Harry Poole
    - Commencement marshals under colors, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00020; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Color guards; negatives (photographic)
    - Honorary degree recipients on stairs of Ballou, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00021; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Ballou Hall; Commencement; negatives (photographic)
    - Commencement audience on the Green, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00022; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Audiences; negatives (photographic)
    - Commencement audience viewed from Barnum Hall, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00023; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Commencement attendees through window of Ballou Hall, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00024; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Ballou Hall; Commencement --Windows; negatives (photographic)
    - Students receiving diplomas at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00025; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Students; negatives (photographic)
    - Students in line at Commencement, 1957-06-09; MS156.001.001.00041.00026; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Reception - Robert Frost, 1957; MS156.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
    S. Tredinnick, not to be mistaken as Frank A. Tredinnick, Jr.
    - Robert Frost speaking with Emily Flint and unidentified man at reception, 1957-11-20; MS156.001.001.00042.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Reception; negatives (photographic); Frost, Robert
    - Robert Frost with John Holmes at reception (1 of 2), 1957-11-20; MS156.001.001.00042.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Other man identified as S. Tredinnick.
      Reception; negatives (photographic); Frost, Robert --Holmes, John A.
    - Robert Frost with John Holmes at reception (2 of 2), 1957-11-20; MS156.001.001.00042.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Robert Frost with English Department at reception, 1957-11-20; MS156.001.001.00042.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Reception --Frost, Robert --English Department; negatives (photographic); Frost, Robert
  - Murals - Alumni Lounge, 1958; MS156.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
    - Mural of men in robes from Alumnae Lounge, 1958-04-15; MS156.001.001.00043.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Murals --Alumnae Lounge; negatives (photographic)
    - Mural of men in suits exchanging paper from Alumnae Lounge, 1958-04-15; MS156.001.001.00043.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Mural of men and woman from Alumnae Lounge, 1958-04-15; MS156.001.001.00043.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Mural of men on campus from Alumnae Lounge, 1958-04-15; MS156.001.001.00043.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Mural of three women and three men from Alumnae Lounge, 1958-04-15; MS156.001.001.00043.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Mural of man with a cape from Alumnae Lounge, 1958-04-15; MS156.001.001.00043.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Tufts Honoraries '58, 1958; MS156.001.001.00044 (Box 1)
    - Honorary degree recipient Reverend Philip Giles, 1958-05-23; MS156.001.001.00044.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Portraits --Giles, Philip; negatives (photographic)
    - Honorary degree recipient John G. Bowker, 1958-05-23; MS156.001.001.00044.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Portraits --Bowker, John G.; negatives (photographic)
    - Honorary degree recipient Robert Kennedy, 1958-05-23; MS156.001.001.00044.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Portraits --Kennedy, Robert; negatives (photographic)
    - Honorary degree recipient General Curtis LeMay, 1958-05-23; MS156.001.001.00044.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Portraits -- LeMay, Gen. Curtis; negatives (photographic)
    - Honorary degree recipient John Walker, 1958-05-23; MS156.001.001.00044.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Portraits --Walker, John; negatives (photographic)
  - Commencement - Tufts, 1958; MS156.001.001.00045 (Box 1)
    - Group of honorary degree recipients at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honoraries; negatives (photographic)
    - Erwin D. Canham speaking at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Speaker --Canham, Erwin D.; negatives (photographic)
    - Joe Stern at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Stern, Joe; negatives (photographic)
    - "3 Swedes," Nils Wessel, Earl Warren, and Arthur J. Anderson at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Wessel, Nils Yngve --Warren, Earl --Anderson, Arthur J.; negatives (photographic)
    - Professor Weaver at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Weaver; negatives (photographic)
    - Reverend Philip Giles receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Giles, Philip; negatives (photographic)
    - Robert Kennedy receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Kennedy, Robert; negatives (photographic)
    - General Curtis LeMay receiving honorary degree at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Lemay, Gen. Curtis; negatives (photographic)
    - General Curtis LeMay receiving hood at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Richard Soderberg receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00010; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Soderberg, Richard; negatives (photographic)
    - Ruth Page Sweet receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Sweet, Ruth Page; negatives (photographic)
    - Myra L. Herrick receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00012; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Herrick, Myra L.; negatives (photographic)
    - John Walker receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00013; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Walker, John; negatives (photographic)
    - John G. Bowker receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00014; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Bowker, John G.; negatives (photographic)
    - Erwin D. Canham receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00015; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Canham, Erwin D.; negatives (photographic)
    - Tredinnick-Marshal at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00016; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Marshals --Tredinnick; negatives (photographic)
    - Van Bush with camera at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00017; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Van Bush; negatives (photographic)
    - Billy Ransom speaking with two women at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00018; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Ransom, Billy; negatives (photographic)
    - Group of Bouve Honors Students at Commencement, 1958-06-08; MS156.001.001.00045.00019; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honors Students --Bouve; negatives (photographic)
  - Robert Frost, 1958; MS156.001.001.00046 (Box 1)
    - Robert Frost speaking with student (who has his eyes closed), 1958-11-24; MS156.001.001.00046.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Frost, Robert --Student; negatives (photographic)
    - Robert Frost (with eyes closed) speaking with student, 1958-11-24; MS156.001.001.00046.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Robert Frost speaking with group (1 of 2), 1958-11-24; MS156.001.001.00046.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Frost, Robert --Student --Group; negatives (photographic)
    - Robert Frost speaking with group (2 of 2), 1958-11-24; MS156.001.001.00046.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Commencement - Tufts, 1959; MS156.001.001.00047 (Box 1)
    - Group of honorary degree recipients at Commencement, 1959-06-07; MS156.001.001.00047.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honoraries --Portraits, Group; negatives (photographic)
    - Robert C. Sprague speaking at Commencement, 1959-06-07; MS156.001.001.00047.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Speaker --Sprague, Robert C.; negatives (photographic)
    - Robert C. Sprague receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1959-06-07; MS156.001.001.00047.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Sprague, Robert C.; negatives (photographic)
    - Francis Henry Russell receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1959-06-07; MS156.001.001.00047.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Russell, Francis Henry; negatives (photographic)
    - John Joseph Mahoney receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1959-06-07; MS156.001.001.00047.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Mahoney, John Joseph; negatives (photographic)
    - Mary G. Mueller receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1959-06-07; MS156.001.001.00047.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees Mueller, Mary G.; negatives (photographic)
    - Robert Frost receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1959-06-07; MS156.001.001.00047.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Frost, Robert; negatives (photographic)
    - Edwin Williams Rawlings receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1959-06-07; MS156.001.001.00047.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Rawlings, Edwin Williams; negatives (photographic)
    - John Roy McLane receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1959-06-07; MS156.001.001.00047.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --McLane, John Roy; negatives (photographic)
    - Henry H. Schooley receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1959-06-07; MS156.001.001.00047.00010; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Schooley, Henry H.; negatives (photographic)
    - 25 year Marshal with Nils Wessell at Commencement, 1959-06-07; MS156.001.001.00047.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Marshal --Wessell, Nils Yngve; negatives (photographic)
    - Marshal and Tredinnick passing color guard at Commencement, 1959-06-07; MS156.001.001.00047.00012; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Marsals --Tredinnick; negatives (photographic)
    - Marshal and Tredinnick followed by color guard at Commencement, 1959-06-07; MS156.001.001.00047.00013; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Marshal --Tredinnick; negatives (photographic)
  - Dr. Carpenter and Jumbo - Tufts, 1959; MS156.001.001.00048 (Box 1)
    - Dr. Carpenter and Jumbo, 1959-07-08; MS156.001.001.00048.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Dr. Carpenter --Jumbo; negatives (photographic)
  - Robert Frost - Tufts, 1959; MS156.001.001.00049 (Box 1)
    - Robert Frost with group, 1959-12-04; MS156.001.001.00049.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Frost, Robert --Group; negatives (photographic)
    - Robert Frost with group, 1959-12-04; MS156.001.001.00049.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Robert Frost exiting Department of Classics office, 1959-12-04; MS156.001.001.00049.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Frost, Robert --Department of Classics; negatives (photographic)
  - Architectural Interiors and Exteriors, 1959 -- 1960; MS156.001.001.00050 (Box 1)
    - Exterior view of Metcalf Hall (?) (1 of 2), 1959 -- 1960; MS156.001.001.00050.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views --Metcalf Hall; negatives (photographic)
    - Exerior front view of Hall (?), 1959 -- 1960; MS156.001.001.00050.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views; negatives (photographic)
    - Exterior view of Metcalf Hall (?) (2 of 2), 1959 -- 1960; MS156.001.001.00050.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Exterior view of Hall (?), 1959 -- 1960; MS156.001.001.00050.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Exterior view of Hall (?), 1959 -- 1960; MS156.001.001.00050.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Exterior view of Fletcher, 1959 -- 1960; MS156.001.001.00050.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views --Fletcher; negatives (photographic)
    - Exterior view of Hall (?), 1959 -- 1960; MS156.001.001.00050.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Exterior view of Fletcher (?), 1959 -- 1960; MS156.001.001.00050.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Exterior view of Fletcher (?), 1959 -- 1960; MS156.001.001.00050.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Interior view of Fletcher library (?), 1959 -- 1960; MS156.001.001.00050.00010; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Interior views --Fletcher Library; negatives (photographic)
    - Interior view of Fletcher library (?), 1959 -- 1960; MS156.001.001.00050.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Interior view of Fletcher library (?), 1959 -- 1960; MS156.001.001.00050.00012; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Interior view of a door, 1959 -- 1960; MS156.001.001.00050.00013; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Interior views --Door; negatives (photographic)
    - Interior view of ceiling, 1959 -- 1960; MS156.001.001.00050.00014; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Interior views --Ceiling; negatives (photographic)
    - Interior view of hallway, 1959 -- 1960; MS156.001.001.00050.00015; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Interior views --Hallway; negatives (photographic)
  - Commencement - Tufts, 1960; MS156.001.001.00051 (Box 1)
    - Group of honorary degree recipients at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Admiral Arleigh Burke receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Burke, Arleigh; negatives (photographic)
    - Raymond Sanger Wilkins receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Wilkins, Raymond Sanger; negatives (photographic)
    - Alexis S. Liatis receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Liatis, Alexis; negatives (photographic)
    - Joseph A. Erickson receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Erickson, Joseph A.; negatives (photographic)
    - John Franklin Enders receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Enders, John Franklin; negatives (photographic)
    - Roy Wood receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Wood, Roy; negatives (photographic)
    - David Brickman receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Brickman, David; negatives (photographic)
    - John Anthony Ciardi receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Ciardi, John Anthony; negatives (photographic)
    - Dana McLean Greeley receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00010; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Greeley, Dana McLean; negatives (photographic)
    - Hiram Leong Fong receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Fong, Hiram Leong; negatives (photographic)
    - Honoraris with Hawaiian leis at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00012; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honoraries --Leis --Group; negatives (photographic)
    - "4 Swedes," Nils Wessel, Earl Warren, Arthur J. Anderson, and Admiral Arleigh Burke at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00013; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Wessel, Nils Yngve --Warren, Earl --Anderson, Arthur J. --Burke, Arleigh; negatives (photographic)
    - Marshal and Wessel at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00014; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Wessel, Nils Yngve --Marshal; negatives (photographic)
    - Marshal and Tredinnick followed by color guard at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00015; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Hiram Leong Fong speaking at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00016; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Speaker --Fong, Hiram Leong; negatives (photographic)
    - Tredinnick standing on a chair speaking at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00017; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Tredinnick; negatives (photographic)
    - Ciel with Fong at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00018; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Fong, Hiram Leong --Ciel; negatives (photographic)
    - Men speaking at Commencement, 1960-06-12; MS156.001.001.00051.00019; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement; negatives (photographic)
  - Exteriors - Tufts Campus, 1960; MS156.001.001.00052 (Box 1)
    - Exterior view of Hodgdon Hall entrance, 1960-07-08; MS156.001.001.00052.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views --Hodgdon Hall; negatives (photographic)
    - Exterior view of Fletcher dorms (?), 1960-07-08; MS156.001.001.00052.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Exterior view of Dewick McPhie (?) Dining Hall, 1960-07-08; MS156.001.001.00052.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views --Dewick McPhie Dining Hall(?); negatives (photographic)
  - Robert Frost - Alumni Hall, 1960; MS156.001.001.00053 (Box 1)
    - Left angle view of Robert Frost speaking at Alumnae Hall, 1960-12-14; MS156.001.001.00053.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Frost, Robert --Alumnae Hall; negatives (photographic)
    - Right angle view of Robert Frost speaking at Alumnae Hall, 1960-12-14; MS156.001.001.00053.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Architectural Exterior, 1961; MS156.001.001.00054 (Box 1)
    - Exterior view of Ballou Hall and Goddard Chapel, 1961-05-03; MS156.001.001.00054.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views --Ballou Hall --Goddard Chapel; negatives (photographic)
    - Exterior view of Ballou Hall and Goddard Chapel, 1961-05-03; MS156.001.001.00054.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Anderson Hall - Exteriors, 1951 -- 1961; MS156.001.001.00055 (Box 1)
    - Right angle exterior view of Anderson Hall from hill, 1961-06-05; MS156.001.001.00055.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views --Anderson Hall; negatives (photographic)
    - Left angle exterior view of Anderson Hall from hill, 1961-06-05; MS156.001.001.00055.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Left angle exterior view of Anderson Hall entrance, 1961-06-05; MS156.001.001.00055.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views --Anderson Hall --Entrance; negatives (photographic)
    - Right angle exterior view of Anderson Hall entrance, 1961-06-05; MS156.001.001.00055.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Right angle exterior view of Anderson Hall entrance, 1961-06-05; MS156.001.001.00055.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Rear exterior view of Anderson Hall, 1961-06-05; MS156.001.001.00055.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Plaques - Anderson Hall, 1951 -- 1961; MS156.001.001.00056 (Box 1)
    - Anderson Hall Plaque for Class of 1910, 6 1/2", 1961-07-11; MS156.001.001.00056.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Anderson Hall --Plaques --Class of 1910; negatives (photographic)
    - Anderson Hall Plaque for Class of 1935, 6 1/2", 1961-07-11; MS156.001.001.00056.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Anderson Hall --Plaques --Class of 1935; negatives (photographic)
    - Anderson Hall Plaque for Class of 1919, 6 1/2", 1961-07-11; MS156.001.001.00056.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Anderson Hall --Plaques --Class of 1919; negatives (photographic)
    - Anderson Hall Plaque for Class of 1921, 6 1/2", 1961-07-11; MS156.001.001.00056.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Anderson Hall --Plaques --Class of 1921; negatives (photographic)
    - Anderson Hall Plaque for Class of 1934, 6 1/2", 1961-07-11; MS156.001.001.00056.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Anderson Hall --Plaques --Class of 1934; negatives (photographic)
    - Anderson Hall Plaque for Frank B. Sanborn, 8", 1961-07-11; MS156.001.001.00056.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Anderson Hall --Plaques --Sanborn, Frank B.; negatives (photographic)
    - Anderson Hall Plaque for Henry L. Vose, 6 1/2", 1961-07-11; MS156.001.001.00056.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Anderson Hall --Plaques --Vose, Henry L. --Class of 1909; negatives (photographic)
    - Anderson Hall Plaque for Class of 1949, 6 1/2", 1961-07-11; MS156.001.001.00056.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Anderson Hall --Plaques --Class of 1949; negatives (photographic)
    - Anderson Hall Plaque for Class of 1936, 6 1/2", 1961-07-11; MS156.001.001.00056.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Anderson Hall --Plaques --Class of 1936; negatives (photographic)
    - Anderson Hall Plaque for Charles P. Atwood, 8", 1961-07-11; MS156.001.001.00056.00010; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Anderson Hall --Plaques --Atwood, Charles P. --Class of 1910; negatives (photographic)
    - Anderson Hall Plaque for Carol Rabb Goldberg, 1961-07-11; MS156.001.001.00056.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Anderson Hall --Plaques --Goldberg, Carol Rabb; negatives (photographic)
    - Anderson Hall Plaque for Vannevar Bush, 8", 1961-07-11; MS156.001.001.00056.00012; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Anderson Hall --Plaques --Bush, Vannevar --Class of 1913; negatives (photographic)
    - Anderson Hall Plaque for Class of 1933, 6 1/2", 1961-07-11; MS156.001.001.00056.00013; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Anderson Hall --Plaques --Class of 1933; negatives (photographic)
    - Anderson Hall Plaque for Class of 1926, 6 1/2", 1961-07-11; MS156.001.001.00056.00014; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Anderson Hall --Plaques --Class of 1926; negatives (photographic)